<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teaching on Vincent Armentano</title>
    <link>/teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teaching on Vincent Armentano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Courses</title>
      <link>/teaching/courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/courses/</guid>
      <description>Machine Learning for Causal Inference with R Syllabus and content forthcoming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TA Work</title>
      <link>/teaching/ta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/ta/</guid>
      <description>ECON1: Principles of Microeconomics, Fall 2021 Each week of the ten week quarter I held an discussion section reviewing course content and helping students perform practice problems. I also held office hours, helped create exam questions and helped ensure lectures ran smoothly by answering questions in the lecture hall and on discord.
ECON3: Principles of Macroeconomics, Winter 2022 For this course I specialized in covering topics of inflation and monetary policy for discussion sections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extracurricular Service</title>
      <link>/teaching/extracurricular/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/extracurricular/</guid>
      <description>Service outside of the classroom is something very important to me. Wherever possible I hope to foster a love of economics in students and see extracurriculuars as a great way to do that.
Graduate Student Research Seminar (GSRS) The Graduate Student Research Seminar (GSRS) is a weekly seminar for graduate students to present ongoing works to other graduate students. Alongside one other student, I help organize this seminar series each quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
